Hey, I'm all packed
and ready to go.
That's right.
Daddy and Uncle Joey
are going on a trip today.
We're going to a conference
in Barbados.
Right?
Uh-huh.
Can you say Barbados?
Barbados.
I got to say,
it means so much to me
that you guys are coming
all the way over there
to hear me give my speech.
Ooh, and I have
a surprise.
I had to pull some strings,
but I was able to get everyone
passes to the entire conference.
That's right!
These babies will
get you into all
the paleontology
lectures and seminars.
Do you have anything
that will get us out of them?
CHANDLER:
Yeah, Ross, I mean,
we're excited
to hear the speech,
but the rest of the time,
we're going to want
to do, you know,
island stuff.
I think David will probably
want to hear a few lectures.
Oh, right, because
he's a scientist.
No, no, well,
because, you know,
he's been in Minsk
for eight years,
and if he gets too much
direct sunlight, he'll die.
Okay, we better go.
So we'll see
you guys tomorrow.
All right, let's do it.
Five-hour flight with Charlie,
have a couple drinks,
get under that blanket
and do what comes natural.
It's a blanket, Joe,
not a cloak of invisibility.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Wow. This place
is beautiful.
Look at all these
paleontologists!
I know. There are going
to be some pasty folks
by the pool tomorrow.
Oh, my God, I can't
believe you're here.
I think I've been recognized.
This happens all the time.
Dr. Geller, I am
such a huge fan.
That never happens.
I've been following
your career for years.
I can't wait for
your keynote speech.
Wow. This is
very flattering.
I would love
your autograph.
Uh... sure.
Um... Dear...
Sarah.
Sarah...
I... dig you.
Dr. Ross Geller.
Oh, thank you so much.
Sure. Oh, and, Sarah,
like to introduce you
to my colleague,
Professor Wheeler.
And this is
Joey Tribbiani.
Are you a paleontologist?
Oh, God, no, no.
No, no, I'm an actor.
You probably recognize me
from a little show called
The Days of Our Lives.
Dude, it's just
Days of Our Lives.
There's no "the."
( chuckling ):
Okay, Ross.
Boy, this guy... yeah.
No, I play Dr. Drake Ramoray.
I'm sorry, I don't own a TV.
You don't own a TV?
What's all your furniture
pointed at?
David, can
you help me?
I'm trying to explain
to Chandler
how a plane stays
in the air.
Oh, certainly.
that's a combination
of Bernoulli's Principle
and Newton's Third Law
of Motion.
See?
Yeah, that's the same as
"it has something
to do with wind."
All right, I'm going to go
pick up a few things
for the trip.
Oh, I should
go, too.
Tomorrow-- do you guys want
to share a cab to the airport,
or should Mike and I
just meet you there?
( laughing ):
Mike? Who's Mike?
Mike's your-your
ex, uh, boyfriend.
That's right! Oh, yeah.
Wow. I had totally
forgotten about him.
That's a... that's a
blast from the past.
It's okay.
Honest mistake.
It really doesn't
mean anything.
I mean, you know...
Monica refers to Chandler
as Richard all the time.
She does?
Let's get you out of here.
Well, at least you
took me down with you.
I'm so sorry.
I just... I keep thinking
about Mike.
I'm crazy about David,
and we're having
so much fun together.
Why-why do I miss Mike?
That's just... that's-that's
going to go away, right?
I guess, in time.
Yeah.
I mean, my feelings for
Richard are certainly gone.
You just did it again.
Chandler-- your feelings
for Chandler are certainly gone.
Boy, Phoebe's still
pretty hung up
on that Mike, huh?
I wouldn't read
too much into it.
Still, you know,
a girl calls you
by her ex-boyfriend's name,
that's not a good thing,
right?
David, let me stop you there,
'cause I think I see
where this is going.
I'm not very good
at giving advice.
See, if you want advice,
go to Ross, Monica
or Joey if the thing
you want advice about
is pizza toppings
or a burning sensation
when you pee.
Sorry, I just... wish there was
something I could do, you know?
Well-well, you know Phoebe...
Seriously,
we're going to do this?
I'm sorry.
I just wish I could
make her forget
about Mike already,
you know?
Why did Phoebe and Mike
break up?
Because his penis was too big.
( chuckles )
I'm sorry. That's
the kind of thing I do.
They broke up because
Mike didn't want
to get married.
Hey, what if you just
let Phoebe know
you'd be open to marriage?
That's great.
That's... that's great.
I'll propose to her.
What?
Well, I was probably
going to do it at some point.
I didn't mean now.
Well, why not?
It's brilliant.
Good-bye, Mike.
We'll see you
at the wedding, fella.
Well, we probably
won't invite you
to the wedding, but...
Thank you, Chandler.
Sincerely, thank you.
Well, you're welcome.
Glad I could help.
How do you think
I should propose?
David, I'm pretending
to read here.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. How you doing? Uh-huh.
Hey, hey.
You said you were
going to wear a thong.
Where's the thong?
I didn't mean a thong.
I meant thongs.
You really should have been
more clear about that.
( knocking )
Hey.
You're never going to guess
who I just saw downstairs.
Oh, uh, Britney Spears.
Yeah, she never misses
these conferences.
No, I just saw
Dr. Kenneth Schwartz!
Oh, my God!
I know.
Did you talk to him?
Yeah. What am I going to say
to Kenneth Schwartz?
You could say,
"Hey, Kenny,
how come you're
not Britney Spears?"
You ready to go?
You-you going
to go now?
I thought we
could hang out.
Oh, I can't.
I have seminars all day,
and I promised Ross
I'd look at his speech.
But maybe we could
have dinner later.
Out on the balcony?
It would be romantic.
Will you wear a thong?
I will if you will.
You got yourself
a very weird deal.
I'm good.
I have dinner plans, so...
So, you going
to be okay?
Yeah, yeah.
I got tons of stuff
I could do.
I'm going to hit the beach,
go swimming...
Joe, have you looked outside?
No. Why?
Oh, man!
There's an indoor pool.
You could
swim there.
Yeah.
I wasn't going to swim.
I was going to dig a hole.
Wow, that "Mike" thing
was interesting.
I don't know what's
going to happen with
Phoebe and David.
I do.
Want a hint, huh?
Okay, I'm sensing this is
some kind of wordplay,
because you are pink
with barely controlled glee.
David's going
to propose to Phoebe.
What?!
Why?!
Because we were talking
about ways
that he could beat Mike,
and I told him that
Phoebe wanted to get married.
Chandler, we have
talked about this.
You are not supposed
to give people advice.
Now, couldn't
you have made
some sort of
inappropriate joke?
I did!
A penis one.
Just so I know, what was
so wrong about what I said?
They've only been going
out for a few weeks.
Phoebe is completely
hung up on Mike.
She'll say no,
David's heart will be broken,
it'll be too hard for them
to recover from,
and then Phoebe will end up
alone again.
Man, that's some bad advice.
Oh, hey.
Thank God you guys are here.
What-what's going on?
Everything is
upside down here.
It rains all day long,
nobody watches TV,
and Ross is famous.
All right, I don't want
to alarm anybody,
but Monica's hair is
twice as big as it was
when we landed.
Okay, when I go places
with high humidity,
it gets a little
extra body, okay?
That's why our
honeymoon photos look
like me and Diana Ross.
Come on, I'll show you guys
where to check in.
Oh, honey...
make sure we get
a king-size bed.
Oh, David, get one
for us, too.
Oh, and see if they have
a heart-shaped one.
And with mirrors
on the ceiling.
And make sure our room
isn't next to theirs.
Oh, you guys are so lucky
you're here with people.
You know, it's just
such a romantic place.
That's all-- I just
wish I could...
share it with
a guy.
Not Joey.
Not Joey, no.
I was... I was just
lusting after Chandler.
Yeah, right.
So, um...
I'm proposing
to Phoebe tonight.
Tonight?
Isn't an engagement ring
supposed to have a diamond?
Oh, there it is.
Yes, well, being
a failed scientist
doesn't pay quite as well
as you might think.
That's um, that's
1/70 of a karat.
And the clarity is...
is quite poor.
Nice.
Monica, can I talk to you
for a second?
Okay.
David's going to propose
to Phoebe tonight.
See what happens when you
give people advice?
I hope you told him not to.
That would be advice!
Okay, fine. I'll handle this.
Phoebe.
Yes?
I need to talk to you.
Are you leaving
the Supremes?
Okay, my husband
just gave your boyfriend
some very bad advice.
David's going to propose
to you tonight.
Wow. Really?
That's fantastic.
What? Are you serious?
You want to marry him?
What about Mike?
Oh, okay, you want me
to marry Mike?
All right, well, let's just
gag him and handcuff him
and force him down
the aisle, okay?
I mean, I can just see it.
"Mike, do you take Phoebe?"
( muffled protest )
You know, it's
every girl's dream.
Do you really think
that marrying someone else
is the right answer?
Sure.
Look, okay, bottom line--
I love Mike... David!
Uh... David.
I love David.
Don't look at me that way,
Roseanne Roseannadanna.
"By using CT scans
and computer imaging,
"we can, in a very real way,
bring the Mesozoic Era
into the 21st century."
It's great.
You're going to be the
hit of the conference.
Oh, and you know what?
It'll be even better tomorrow
because I won't be constantly
interrupted by Joey
checking to see if they put
chocolates on my pillow yet.
( knocking )
Hey, guys.
The chocolates
aren't here yet.
Damn it!
Ross just read me
his speech.
It's fantastic.
Oh, is it on the computer?
'Cause I'd love
to give it a read.
If you want to check
your e-mail, just ask.
What? May I?
What's with the rain, Geller?
I mean, when I signed up
for dino week,
nobody said anything
about it being monsoon season.
Actually, the wet season
is June to December.
It's not the time, Charlie.
No, no! Dear God, no!
Oh, what, did
someone outbid you
for the teapot?
Secret teapot?
Your computer,
I don't know wha...
Everything's gone.
What do you mean?
It must be a virus.
I think it erased
your hard drive.
What?
Oh, my God.
What did you do?
Someone I don't know
sent me an e-mail,
and I opened it.
Why? Why would you open it?
Well, it didn't say
"This is a virus."
What did it say?
"Nude...
pictures of Anna Kournikova."
I'm so sorry.
What am I going to do?
My speech is gone, Chandler.
It's not gone.
I mean, I'm sure you
printed out a copy.
You have a hard copy, right?
No, I don't!
Well, you must be
pretty mad
at yourself right now.
It's really gone?
Yep.
I'd like to thank you guys
for coming down here
to complain about the rain
and ruin my career.
I just feel awful.
Yeah, you should.
Nude pictures
of Anna Kournikova?
She's never even won
a major tournament.
Well, I tried
Billie Jean King, but...
You know,
you and Monica have
the same "I'm going
to kill you" look.
I can usually
make it go away
by kissing her.
Get out.
You know, this happens
all the time
to my computer at work.
Well, what do you do?
Well, I usually go play Tetris
on somebody else's computer.
I can't believe this.
I can't believe
this is happening.
I have to give
the keynote speech
tomorrow, okay?
I have to stand up
in front of all these people.
What am I going to say?
I could teach you
a speech
that I memorized
for auditions.
I don't think
your monologue from Star Wars
is going to help me
right now, Joe.
Ross, Ross,
we can solve this.
I just heard your speech.
We can recreate it.
We've got all night.
You really think
we can do that?
Oh, wait.
Joey and I are supposed
to have dinner.
Hey, don't worry about that.
I mean, Ross needs you,
you know?
And Rachel and I will stay
and help any way we can.
( groans )
All right.
Okay, let's do it.
Um, I know we start
by discussing the shortcomings
of carbon dating.
And then, then I move on
to what is clearly
the defining moment
of the Mesozoic Era--
the breakup of Pangaea-- hello.
And then there's the overview
of the Triassic.
Ooh, ooh, any chance
any of this happened
in a galaxy far,
far away?
( sputtering )
( phone rings )
Hello?
Okay, Mike,
enough is enough.
Now, you love Phoebe
and she loves you,
so you need to get over
your whole
"I never want to get
married" thing
and step up!
Who is this?
This is Monica.
I'm Phoebe's friend.
Listen, Phoebe is back
with David,
and he's going
to propose to her,
and she's going to say yes,
but I know she really wants
to be with you.
He's, he's going to propose?
I'm sorry.
Did you say something?
I can't hear through
all this damned hair!
Look, if Phoebe wants
to marry David, she should.
I'm not going to stand
in the way of that.
Neither should you.
You don't tell me what to do.
I tell you what to do.
Just call her.
She's at the Paradise Hotel
in Barbados.
And while I've got you,
you've got curly hair.
What do you do in the humidity?
Damn it!
Well, I hope you're happy.
Aw, I hope you're
happy too, honey.
Phoebe's going to say yes
to David.
See? That's what happens when
you meddle in people's lives.
Phoebe's going
to say yes?
That's great.
No, it's not! Because
she's still in love with Mike!
And there's no chance
that will work?
No, I called him.
It's not going to happen.
( gasps ):
Meddler! Meddler!
Well, if you hadn't meddled
to start with,
then I wouldn't have had
to go in there
and meddle myself!
Now no matter
how much we meddle,
we'll never be able
to unmeddle the thing
that you meddled up
in the first place!
This vacation sucks!
I'm so bored.
Mm.
Stupid rain.
We can't do anything.
Well, I brought some books.
We could read.
Hey, it hasn't come
to that yet, okay?
Hey, hey, hey,
don't mind if I do.
I'm sorry, sir.
These are for the
pharmaceutical convention.
Hey, Rach, you feel like
going to a convention?
We can't.
We're not pharmacists.
I know we're not,
but, uh...
Frank Madeo and...
Ava Churara...
wumba... wum...
"Kate Miller."
Kate Miller it is.
Okay.
And that's the most sex
I'm going to have
this weekend.
Well, in that case,
should I make sure
it's on real good?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Uh, and then, and then
you said that thing
about, about bringing
the Mesozoic Era
into the 21st century.
Well, yeah. That's it?
Yeah.
Oh, my God!
We did it!
Actually,
I did it, Ross.
You remembered
shockingly little
of your own speech.
Yes, but I did make
a pyramid
out of the bath products.
This is, this is amazing.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
That, that's a pretty necklace.
Thank you.
Hey, what do you say
we celebrate?
Champagne?
Oh, yeah!
Hey, save the cork,
and that way, we can fill
the bottle with water
and put it back
so they don't charge you.
Oh, my God, I love you.
Oh, this is such a cute picture
of Emma.
And is this your son
or just some kid whose picture
you bring on vacation?
Yeah, that's Ben,
my son from my first marriage.
Your first marriage?
Yeah.
You've been married
more than once?
No, no.
So, why'd you break up?
Oh, it was...
complicated, you know?
She, uh, she was...
gay.
Oh, my God!
This is so cool!
Okay, odd thing
to get excited about.
No, it's just that
I was engaged to a guy
who turned out to be gay.
Hey! High five!
Didn't you feel
so stupid
that you didn't
see the signs?
My fiance was always going
away on these long weekends
with his tennis partner.
My wife had
a workout friend
she went
to the gym with
every day for a year.
She didn't get
any fitter.
Right, and everybody
finds out,
and they're, like,
"Oh, I knew all along."
I know. If you knew,
why didn't you tell me,
you know?
I mean, call, leave a note.
"Hi, just dropped by
to say your wife's gay."
I know!
And then you try to make
the best of a bad situation
so you float the idea
of a threesome.
I didn't do that.
Me, neither.
Well, who knew?
Pharmacists are fun.
I know.
That old lady
at the end
was ready
to take you home.
Not enough pills
in the world, Rach.
But what about you, huh?
You're the single one.
See anybody in there
you like?
Well, let's see.
There was that
really big guy
that I was talking to
with the really
nice breasts.
But what about back home?
Anything going on there?
Anybody you like?
No.
There is.
You're blushing.
No, I'm not blushing.
I'm sunburned.
From, you know, the rain.
You like someone.
Tell me who it is.
Who is it?
No. Joey!
Come on, who?
Who do you like? Tell me.
You're not getting away
that easy.
Stop it.
Joey, come on!
It doesn't matter,
you know?
It's not like anything's
going to happen.
What?
Why not?
Rach, who can you not get?
( scoffs )
Okay, okay.
You really want
to know who it is?
Yeah. Who is it?
Do you?
Yeah.
Hey.
I just left you
a message.
Ross and I were going
to go grab a bite,
but now that you're here,
maybe we could go
have that dinner.
Right. Of course.
Hey, did you guys
finish the speech?
Yep, we got it.
We got it.
Thank you so much.
I had a great time.
Yeah.
Hey, look,
and this isn't over,
because I really want
to know who...
Later, later.
So, um, shall we?
Yeah.
Okay. Bye.
Okay, good night.
Night.
( sighs )
Okay, good night.
Night, Ross.
I can't believe she's going
to say yes to David
when she's clearly in love
with Mike.
You know, it's very hard
to take you seriously
when you look like that.
Um...
Phoebe, um, I have, uh,
something I want to say.
Oh, my God,
he's going to do it now.
Please, I cannot watch this.
Let's go.
I think we have some time.
Have you ever heard him talk?
"Uh, Phoebe, um, I would be
honored if, uh, uh..."
Spit it out, David!
Um, Phoebe, um...
Well, you're an amazing woman,
and the time
we spent apart was,
was... unbearable.
Of course, the sanitation
strikes in Minsk didn't help.
Sure, okay, yeah.
But, um, well, now
that we're together again,
I don't ever want to be apart.
So to that end...
Oh, my God, Mike.
It's David, actually.
No, Mike's here.
Oh, hey, Mike.
Hi, David.
Chandler.
Moni... Oh.
It's the humidity!
Hi, Phoebe.
What are you doing here?
I have a question
I need to ask you.
I was kind of going
to ask her myself.
Yeah, I understand,
but before you do,
she really needs
to hear this.
Okay.
Would you care
for my seat as well?
Actually, yeah, that'd be great.
Well, that's fair.
You've had a long trip.
Phoebe, I love you.
I've missed you so much
these last few months.
And I thought we were
apart for a good reason.
But then,
I suddenly realized
that there was no reason
good enough
to keep me from spending
the rest of my life with you.
Uh... I-I...
this kind of steps on the toes
of what I was going to say.
I'm sorry, David.
But she really
has to know this.
All right, but after this,
I want to see you outside.
If the rain stops.
You're the most
incredible woman
I've ever met.
How could I lose you?
Now, I don't actually
have a ring.
I-I-I have a ring.
I wouldn't brag too much
about that thing, big guy.
Phoebe...
will you marry me?
No.
Um... ha-ha.
I love you.
But I never needed
a proposal from you.
I just needed to know
that we were headed somewhere.
You know, that we had a future.
We can have
any future you want.
Okay, well, I'm, uh...
I'm gonna take off.
Oh, God, David,
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Just so I know, uh...
if I had asked first...
Yeah, I-I...
I might have said yes.
But that would've been wrong.
I mean...
Please, you don't
have to explain.
Perhaps if I hadn't
gone to Minsk,
things would've
worked out for us.
And I wouldn't have
ruined my career...
or lost that toe to frostbite.
It was a good trip.
Is it okay
if I hug you now?
Yes.
Because of our meddling!
Oh, isn't this nice?
So quiet, I could
just lie here all day.
Oh, I know.
( door opens )
Open your drapes!
So glad we got
adjoining rooms.
The sun is out!
Look!
Hey, remember
when I had corneas?
You go down to the pool
and reserve the chairs,
and I'll get the magazines
and the lotion.
Uh, ladies,
Ross's speech is in 45 minutes.
No!
Damn it!
ROSS:
Walls are pretty
thin, guys.
Then we have to weigh the data
from recent MRI scans
and DNA testing,
which call into question
information gathered from years
of simple carbon dating.
Look at that woman
sitting out by the
pool getting tan.
She's all leathery
and wrinkled.
I'm so jealous!
Finally, factor in
the profusion of new species
recently discovered:
Giganotosaurus.
Argentinosaurus.
Not to mention
"Coldsaurus."
And that's just the herbivores.
I'm not even going to discuss
the carnivores.
Their heads are already too big.
Which is ironic
considering their stunted
cerebral development.
( laughing )
( laughing heartily )
Really?
But all kidding aside...
In much the same way
that Homo ergaster
is now thought to be a separate
species from Homo erectus...
( laughs )
What?
He said "erectus."
You're kidding, right?
No, he really said it.
And while there are certainly
vast differences
between these Mesozoic fossils
and the example
of Homo erectus...
( laughs )
Erectus?
Homo.
( laughs )
In a very real way,
we can bring the Mesozoic Era
into the 21st century.
Thank you.
( applause )
Congratulations.
Great.
Really?
Really great.
Oh, thanks, guys.
I thought it
was wonderful.
Oh.
Jarvis Oberblau. Cornell.
I mean, the ideas
you put forth.
And from someone
so young and...
Okay, now we're
just holding hands.
All right.
Well, um, we're gonna
hit the beach.
It was really great.
Oh, thank you so much.
And so funny.
Take it easy.
Okay.
All right, thanks.
Thanks so much.
I can't tell you
how much it means to me
that you were here.
What, are you kidding?
We wouldn't have missed it.
Oh.
I'm back.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Hey.
Well?
You were incredible.
I mean, you blew
them away.
I can't tell you
how great it was
to look out into the crowd
and see your face.
I mean...
did you know you were
mouthing the words
along with me?
I was not.
No, it's okay. It made me
feel like a rock star.
Oh, my God,
I'm your groupie.
I better not find you
naked in my hotel room.
Look, I took it too far.
Oh, I can't believe
it's raining again.
It's so unfair.
Well, on the bright side,
now we won't have to see
all these paleontologists
with their shirts off.
Not you guys.
You've got it going on.
So what are we
gonna do today?
They have a game
room downstairs.
I think they have like,
ping-pong and stuff.
Ping-pong?!
Honey, they have ping-pong.
Let's play.
I don't think so.
Why not?
Because you know how
competitive you get.
And while I say
it's cute,
others disagree
and I'm lying.
I'm not always that bad.
Oh, yeah?
What happened when
we played last time?
I punched you.
And...?
Phoebe.
I clunked
your heads together.
( blows )
( chuckles )
Hey. There you are.
Hey, listen, as soon
as it stops raining,
we have got to go
snorkeling.
Some kid told me
about this sea turtle
and if you blow bubbles
in his face, he chases you.
I'm sorry, I can't.
I'm running a discussion group
all afternoon.
Oh. Well, that's okay.
I'll find someone
else to do it.
I'd do it alone, but, uh...
I don't know what happens
if the sea turtle catches you.
God, you know,
I feel so bad.
I haven't seen you
this whole trip.
Especially last night.
Hey, don't worry about it.
It was fine.
I ended up having the
best time with Rachel.
I just felt bad for you,
stuck in that room
working on Ross's speech.
Actually, it turned out
to be a lot of fun.
Oh.
Well, at least
we're both having fun.
Is it weird that
it's not with each other?
Yeah.
A little bit, yeah.
I think we need to talk.
Yeah, I think we do.
About what?
Come on, you guys,
it'll be fun.
All right, all right,
I'll play if we
don't keep score.
Well, then how do we know
who wins?
Nobody wins.
So we're just four losers.
Super!
Well, I'm not
playing with her.
I'm out.
I'll play you.
Okay.
Mike, you don't know
what you're doing.
She gets crazy.
This scar is from Pictionary.
I think I'll be all right.
You want to volley a bit
for serve?
Sure if you want to.
Oh!
Oh, by the way, um, I'm awesome.
Oh, dear God,
there's two of them.
You ready to play?
Hell, yeah.
Did you know this
about him?
No idea.
I thought he was
soft like you.
You want to make it
more interesting?
How much were you thinking?
Ten bucks a game.
Make it 50.
I'll make it a hundred.
One thousand...
Okay!
We'll flip to see
who goes first.
You got a quarter?
No.
Either of you girls
got a quarter?
Honey, try to focus
the trash talk on him.
Monica, you call it.
Heads.
No, tails! Heads!
Tails.
Oh, what are the chances?!
Ha! My point!
Oh, no, I don't
think so.
According to standard table
tennis rules,
if at any time a player uses
his non-racquet-bearing hand
to touch the playing surface,
he or she forfeits the point.
He was a lawyer.
All of the East Coast
is having beautiful weather.
In New York it's 72 and sunny.
Weather bitch.
( knocking on door )
It's open.
Hi, Joe.
Hey.
What, is everything okay?
Charlie and I broke up.
No. Why?
Well, she said
we have nothing in common.
That's crazy.
No, it's not.
We have nothing in common.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, she should be with
someone more like... Ross.
You know, he uses
all those big words, too.
Man, smart people are dull.
Hey!
( chuckles )
Okay, Rach.
I feel so stupid, you know.
Why do I keep going after
the wrong girls?
Well, what are you
talking about?
Come on, I mean,
there's you,
then there's Charlie...
That's like...
( sighs )
What the hell's
my problem?
( sighs )
Okay. Um...
maybe you're not always
going after the wrong girl.
I'm telling you, Rach,
Charlie is not right for me.
Yeah, I'm not talking about her.
Well, then who?
The waitress I went out with
last month?
You know what?
Forget it.
No, no, no, no,
Who are you
talking about?
I-I-I don't... I don't...
I actually don't know
who I'm talking about.
Okay.
All right, well...
I'm gonna go see if I can
get a room for tonight.
And, uh,
I'll see you later.
Yeah, sure. Okay.
You like me?
Okay...
let's not make a big thing
about this.
It's a huge thing.
Okay, not working
with me, Joe.
Look, here's
the thing.
Lately, I have been
having thoughts.
Musings, if you will.
Wha... For how long?
Only like a month.
A month?!
Dial it down.
Listen, okay, and maybe
they're crazy thoughts,
but sometimes I do.
I've been thinking about,
you know, us.
Okay, dial it up a little.
Okay... I just have
one question.
Shoot.
What the hell are you doing?!
I'm not trying to do anything.
It's just, we have such
a good time
when we're together,
you know.
Aren't you just
a little curious
what it would be like?
Am I curious?
I'm as curious as... as...
George.
Who?
Curious George.
You know, the monkey
and the guy with the yellow hat?
Yes, of course.
I remember him.
He had a paper route.
Yeah, he did.
See, this is what
I'm talking about.
Yeah, I know we're great,
but, Rach, no, this...
this can't happen.
Can't it just happen
a little bit?
Well...
No! No!
It can't happen at all!
Why? Why not?
Because, look, no one
wants this to happen
more than me, okay?
I have gone over this moment
in my head a hundred times
and not once did I ever
say no.
But...
( sighs )
I couldn't do it to Ross.
But that wasn't going
to stop you before.
I know.
I know, but I've thought
about it a lot since then,
and it just wouldn't be right.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Oh, God.
I shouldn't have
said anything.
No, no.
No, no, no.
Hey, hey,
we'll be fine.
Like you said,
it's no big deal.
It's not a big deal.
No big deal.
It's so not a big deal.
Yeah.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Hey.
( sighs )
Oh!
Oh! I'm sorry, I think...
I think that may
have missed the table.
Oh, do you?
Uh, yeah.
Do you?
Do ya?
Uh, yeah.
You really find this
attractive on him?
Oh, yeah.
Are you telling me
you're not even
a little turned on
by Monica right now?
I think this is the first time
in our marriage
that I felt like
the more attractive one.
PHOEBE:
All right,
come on, Mike.
You can beat her.
Knock that dog
off her head.
Damn it!
I sleep with him.
Game point.
Don't get too cocky.
Remember, I won the last one.
Oh, by the way, how did that
feel losing to a girl?
You know, you should really
look in mirror
before you call yourself that.
No! No! No!
And that's how it's done.
CHANDLER:
Okeydokey.
You've each won a game
and I've lost what's felt
like a year of my life.
So everybody goes home a winner.
Best out of three?
That's what I'm thinking.
Should I use my invisibility
to fight crime or for evil?
Serve the ball, chump.
( imitating Monica ):
"Serve the ball, chump."
Okay, better comebacks, Mike.
Better comebacks.
I'm just saying I have
a cabin in the Adirondacks.
And if you ever want to get away
from the city,
well, that'd be...
just nifty.
Ooh, well, um...
I've kind of got a lot
on my plate right now.
Not that I wouldn't love
a weekend in the country
with a strange man.
Jarvis?
Oh, you're back.
Um, this is my wife Nancy.
Get out.
Ross, can I talk
to you for a minute?
Yes, please.
Um, so what's
going on?
Um...
Well...
Joey and I broke up.
Oh, my God.
What... what happened?
Joey is a great guy,
but we're just...
we're so different.
I mean, like during your speech
he kept laughing
at Homo erectus.
I knew that was him.
Anyway, I just...
I think
it's for the best.
Hey. Hey, you okay?
I guess.
There was, um...
there was another reason
that I thought it was
time to end it with Joey.
I started to realize that
I was having feelings
for someone else.
Okay, Geller, last day
of the conference.
You know what happens
to the keynote speaker.
Uh, Professor Klarik,
we're kind of in the middle
of a conversation here.
Yeah. Can't you guys just
throw him in the pool later?
Or we could throw you both
in now.
Okay, gentlemen, please.
Aren't we a little
old for this?
I mean,
we're scientists,
all right?
We're academics,
and most importantly,
you will have
to catch us first.
Go! Go! Go!
Okay, so it's tied again:
41 to 41.
Okay, look, enough
is enough.
No, I just have two more
points to beat him.
Monica, that was
also true an hour ago.
I mean, please,
look at you.
Your hand is blistered.
You can barely stand.
Your hair is inexplicable.
Okay, you've already proven
you're just as good as he is.
Now we've missed our
dinner reservations.
So now let's just go upstairs,
order room service,
take a shower
and shave your head.
I can't just walk away.
I've put in four hours.
But...
Look, you knew this about me
when you married me.
You agreed to take me
in sickness and in health.
Well, this is my sickness.
What about
the obsessive cleaning?
That's just good sense.
Ow!
( stifled moan )
You okay?
No, no, honey,
I'm okay.
I shake it off.
Oh, God, no shaking!
No shaking!
No shaking.
Oh, my God.
I can't play.
So you forfeit?
Mike wins?
I can't believe it.
I lost.
No, you didn't.
What?
Because I'm going
to play for you.
You can't do that.
It's okay.
I don't care which
of them I beat.
Okay, we're taking that paddle
home, mister.
Honey, you don't have
to do this.
Yes, I do.
Now, I may not understand why
you have to win so badly,
but if it's important to you,
then it's important to me.
Because I love you.
But... you suck.
You're welcome, sweetheart.
All right, Mike, let's
get this over with.
Sudden death.
Whoever wins this point, wins.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
You're good.
It's like watching porn.
And that's how it's done.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
That was so amazing.
When did you...?
Hold on, I almost forgot.
Loser!
When did you stop sucking?
I never sucked.
I just didn't
want you to know
how good I was.
Why?
I don't know.
This is so great.
Now we can enter into
doubles tournaments.
That's why.
Are they still
looking for us?
Yeah, yeah, the bartender
said they split up
into two search parties--
the herbivores
and the carnivores.
You know, we as a group,
are not the coolest.
Oh!
I don't think
they saw us.
I don't think they did.
Um, so...
I started to tell
you something earlier.
There... there was
another reason
I realized it was
time to end it with Joey.
I, um, I kind of realized
I was starting to have
feeling for someone else.
Huh.
Can I... can I ask who?
I think you know.
I think I know too, but
I've been really wrong
about this stuff
in the past, so...
I'm sorry.
We, uh... we can't.
All right, all right.
I mean, you just went out
with my best friend, you know.
I just think it would be
a really, really bad idea.
Or not.
What?
Oh.